- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_01_Periville
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_01_Periville_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Galahad_B
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_01_Periville_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Chestwear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_02_Karburg
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Galahad_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Footwear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Galahad_D
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Handwear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_BellaRuby
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Galahad_E
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Headgear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Galahad_E
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionFamilyWardLostT5
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Morgaine_B
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT3
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Morgaine_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_09_Canopus
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Morgaine_D
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Morgaine_D
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_11_Lepus
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99C_Morgaine_D
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CoatingAeternianT5
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99C_MSQ_12_Vector
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99C_MSQ_12_Vector_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Galahad_A
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99C_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99C_MSQ_12_Vector_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ringweaversfent4
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_title"
  Description: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_completion_new_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
